This Halloween, broomsticks are so not happenin'.
Twitches is a comedy, drama, family film directed by Stuart Gillard.
Twins separated at birth, Camryn and Alex meet by chance for the first time on their 21st birthday and discover
they're witches with the power to save their homeland of Coventry from the evil that threatens it.
But when Camryn leaves Alex to face the darkness alone, will Coventry be doomed?
Or will the sisters multiply their magic by standing together?
Alex Fielding / Artemis, played by Tia Mowry.
Camryn Barnes / Apolla, played by Tamera Mowry-Housley.
Miranda, played by Kristen Wilson.
Thantos, played by Patrick Fabian.
Karsh, played by Pat Kelly.
Illeana, played by Jennifer Robertson.
Twitches is a 2005 American fantasy comedy-drama film released as a Disney Channel original
movie and based on the Twitches book series published by Scholastic Press.
Produced by Broomsticks Productions Limited, the film stars Tia Mowry and
Tamera Mowry as Alexandra Fielding and Camryn Barnes, respectively.
A sequel, Twitches Too, aired on October 12, 2007, as a
part of Disney Channel's Hauntober Fest.
The film explores themes of witch, mother, sibling
relationship, parent child relationship, darkness.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.